

Contacts

- ©: +420 777 44 84 27

Tech skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- GIT
- WebPack
- SASS
- JavaScript
- OOP
- Bootstrap
- MS Visual Studio
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- WordPress
- MySQL
- PHP

Soft skills

- Team work
- Working with a large amount of information
- Result orientation
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Responsibility
- Sociability

Language knowledge

- Ukrainian is native
- English B1 Intermediate
- Russian C1 High level
- Czech A1 Entry level
- Poland A1 Entry level

Mariana Machohan

Front-End Developer

I am a half creative person. Worked in the specialty for 9 years. I thought about changing the field of activity a long time ago, but fears that it was not mine that I would not succeed prevailed. One day in the spring of 2021, I had an advertisement to run a marathon for free. At that time I did not have a job, so I decided why not to try. Thanks to the marathon, I realized that it was mine. I didn't want to take the training course that they later offered to take... They taught for too long... I realized that it was mine and wanted to learn everything faster... So I started learning video lessons mainly from YouTube and pure theory database sites... At the moment I am studying JS for courses to get a certificate. Next I will also teach React, also with courses, also to get a certificate. In plans to start my career in IT as FrontEnd developer and go to FullStack in the future.

Sites

- 1. [GitHub]
- 2. [LinkedIn]
- 3. [freeCodeCamp]

Work experience

Architect-designer Freelance

10.2011-11.2020 | Ukraine

- Single-family houses. Working drawings, assemblies, exterior visualization.
- Interior design of houses, apartments and individual residential, non-residential, commercial premises.
- Consultation on zoning, color scheme, stylistic decision.
- Visit to objects and control of the working process.

Tester Freelance

From 16.11.2021 | Czech Republic

- Testing web app with Figma
- Testing data bases in MySQL

Web Developer Freelance

March 2015 - October 2018 | Czech Republic

Landing pages (HTML + CSS)

Education

Lviv National Agrarian University

Architecture

2009 - 2013 Ukraine

Morshyn School of Arts

Art (drawing)

2003 - 2007 Ukraine

Certificates



